[
{"question": "Get data from active directory using react and ASP.NET core", "answers": []},
{"question": "Dark theme does not get apply to webview for react native android app", "answers": []},
{"question": "My VS code is not loading the development server for react JS in browser", "answers": []},
{"question": "Type error: cannot read property 'map' of null - react JS", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    How have you defined products is still not clear. I can just guess that its initialized as null in your component and that is causing an error. \r\n\r\nmap works only on arrays. So, check products is defined array before doing map on it.\r\nTry this and see:\r\nif(products)\r\n{\r\n  products.map((product, index) => (\r\n    <li key={index}>\r\n      <h2>{product.name}</h2>\r\n      <div className=\"space3\"></div>\r\n      <img src={product.image} alt={product.name} />\r\n      <div className=\"space\"></div>\r\n      <div className=\"buy-product\">\r\n        <button onClick={() => (window.location.href = product.link)}>\r\n          Buy\r\n        </button>\r\n      </div>\r\n      <h4>${product.cost}</h4>\r\n      <div className=\"cart-container\">\r\n        <div className=\"space2\"></div>\r\n        <div className=\"product-icon\">\r\n          <a className=\"cart\" onClick={() => addToCart(product)}>\r\n            <FaCartPlus />\r\n          </a>\r\n        </div>\r\n      </div>\r\n    </li>\r\n  ))}\r\n}\r\nIf that doesn't solve, look at the other possible reasons here and troubleshoot: []\r\n12-Nov-20 2:44am\r\n<ul className=\"flex cards\">\r\n          {if (products) {\r\n            products.map((product, index) => (\r\n            <li key={index}>\r\n              <h2>{product.name}</h2>\r\n              <div className=\"space3\"></div>\r\n              <img src={product.image} alt={product.name} />\r\n              <div className=\"space\"></div>\r\n              <div className=\"buy-product\">\r\n                <button onClick={() => (window.location.href = product.link)}>\r\n                  Buy\r\n                </button>\r\n              </div>\r\n              <h4>${product.cost}</h4>\r\n              <div className=\"cart-container\">\r\n                <div className=\"space2\"></div>\r\n                <div className=\"product-icon\">\r\n                  <a className=\"cart\" onClick={() => addToCart(product)}>\r\n                    <FaCartPlus />\r\n                  </a>\r\n                </div>\r\n              </div>\r\n            </li>\r\n          ))\r\n          }}\r\n        </ul>\r\n12-Nov-20 2:51am12-Nov-20 2:55am12-Nov-20 4:30am12-Nov-20 21:35pmHideExpandCopy Codeif (item) {    return (      <div className=\"products\">        <h1 className=\"big-text\">Games</h1>        {/* Cards */}        <div className=\"products\">          <ul className=\"flex cards\">            {products.map((product, index) => (              <li key={index}>                <h2>{product.name}</h2>                <div className=\"space3\"></div>                <img src={product.image} alt={product.name} />                <div className=\"space\"></div>                <div className=\"buy-product\">                  <button onClick={() => (window.location.href = product.link)}>                    Buy                  </button>                </div>                <h4>${product.cost}</h4>                <div className=\"cart-container\">                  <div className=\"space2\"></div>                  <div className=\"product-icon\">                    <a className=\"cart\" onClick={() => addToCart(product)}>                      <FaCartPlus />                    </a>                  </div>                </div>              </li>            ))}          </ul>        </div>      </div>    );  }12-Nov-20 3:59am"]},
{"question": "Which react/JS project should I build for my 1st job portfolio?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It is impossible to answer such a question, without knowing more about you, and more about the jobs that are available. And this site is not the place to find the answers; this is for programming questions. All I would say is, look at other websites and try to see what things are good and what bad, and create a design from what you see and learn.\r\nRichard MacCutchan24-Sep-20 17:16pm24-Sep-20 17:21pm"]},
{"question": "How to pass json object to another activity in react native", "answers": []},
{"question": "Code not reacting to inputs", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    This is my full code\r\n\r\n<pre>package com.company;\r\nimport java.util.Scanner;\r\n\r\npublic class Main {\r\n    //prints string to console\r\n    private static void print(String s) {\r\n        System.out.println(s);\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    //all the constants for given R values returns the correct R value\r\n    private static double rValues(String pressure){\r\n        double R = 0;\r\n        if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"atm\")){\r\n            R = 0.082057338;\r\n        }else if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"tor\")){\r\n            R = 62.363577;\r\n        }else if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"mmHg\")){\r\n            R = 62.36367;\r\n        }\r\n        return R;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    //all of the equations solved for unknown variable\r\n    private static double solve_P(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature ){\r\n        double exitP;\r\n        exitP = (variables[2]*temperature*constant)/variables[1];\r\n        return exitP;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_V(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature){\r\n        double exitV;\r\n        exitV =(variables[2]*temperature*constant)/variables[0];\r\n        return exitV;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_n(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature){\r\n        double exitN;\r\n        exitN = (variables[0]*variables[1])/(constant*temperature);\r\n        return exitN;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_T(double[] variables, double constant){\r\n        double exitT;\r\n        exitT = (variables[0]*variables[1])/(constant*variables[2]);\r\n        return exitT;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n    public static void main(String[] args) {\r\n\r\n        //play again loop\r\n        boolean isRunning = true;\r\n        String playAgain;\r\n        while (isRunning) {\r\n\r\n            Scanner keyboard = new Scanner(System.in);//creates scanner\r\n\r\n            //introduction\r\n            print(\"This is an ideal gas law solver\");\r\n            print(\"PV=nRT\");\r\n\r\n            //what R value to use\r\n            print(\"what is the pressure measured in?\");\r\n            print(\"atm, tor, or mmmHg\");\r\n            print(\">\");\r\n            String whatPressure;\r\n            whatPressure = keyboard.next();\r\n            double rConstant;\r\n            rConstant = rValues(whatPressure);\r\n\r\n            //stored questions\r\n            String[] userQuestions = {\"what is the pressure P\",\r\n                    \"what is the volume V\",\r\n                    \"what is the number of moles n\"};\r\n\r\n            //stores answers in userAnswers\r\n            double[] userAnswers = new double[3];\r\n\r\n            print(\"what variable would you like to solve for?\");\r\n            String unknownVariable;\r\n            unknownVariable = keyboard.next();\r\n            System.out.println(\"solving for \" + unknownVariable);\r\n\r\n            //converts between celsius and kelvin\r\n            double temperature = 0;\r\n            if (unknownVariable.compareToIgnoreCase(\"T\") == 0) {\r\n                print(\"what is the temperature in?\");\r\n                print(\"kelvin (K) or celsius (c) \");\r\n                String whatTemperatureUnit;\r\n                whatTemperatureUnit = keyboard.next();\r\n                print(\"what is the temperature?\");\r\n                temperature = keyboard.nextDouble();\r\n                if (whatTemperatureUnit\r\nMember 1377085311-Apr-18 4:32am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It is not by mistake: your code is  to do that.\r\nCPallini"]},
{"question": "Proper way on how to install and add an audio file in react native?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Sorry, but this site does not provide code to order. And the expression  tells us nothing that would lead us to suggested solutions.\r\nRichard MacCutchan", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It would not work on its own. You have to configure the project to run properly, and also make sure that you are using the valid file types. This package react-audio-player uses the native <audio /> tag to provide the service, and this HTML5 element is known to have some limitations for the file types that it can run ().\r\n\r\nCheck more on the package here at NPM: [] \r\n[]\r\nAfzaal Ahmad Zeeshan"]},
{"question": "React working with disk files", "answers": []},
{"question": "Variable type reacting to sound?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    See [] and  [].\r\nRichard MacCutchan"]},
{"question": "Call react element from HTML", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to react to touchpad scrolling in WPF?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Basically, my advice is in the discussion in comments to the question.\r\n\r\nYou are welcome.\r\n\r\nLet me put some speculations here. I hope we are about to close this issue, because further steps can be out of our reach.\r\n\r\nAccording to your description, your code does nothing by handling the mouse wheel event (next time, better show where you add the event handler to the invocation tree of some event instance, that is, corresponding += operator, because the method name customTileController_MouseWheel, strictly speaking, does not tell anything about it; also, never use such auto-generated names, they violate good Microsoft naming conventions, for some apparent reasons). It cannot be wrong.\r\n\r\nFirst of all, all input events available in .NET are of different levels. Some are primary and are generated by the hardware and are pushed to the system through the hardware interrupts one some IRQ line and handled by the hardware driver, and some are secondary. For example, hardware events produce KeyDown and KeyUp events (also indirectly), but not KeyPress event, which is secondary to the first two; it comes into play after a long chain taking into account input language, to produce a character which does not exist on lower level.\r\n\r\nThis is not what happens to physical mouse wheel. When you roll it, hardware generates the event of the same level as, say, mouse move, even though in mouse move of an optical mouse, optical image recognition takes place. Anyway, , these are the events of the same level. The roll of the mouse cannot be misinterpreted as mouse move.\r\n\r\nWhat happens in the touchpad \"scroll\" area? Nothing like that. Instead, some code is  to emulate the same effect as the \"real mouse\" does. Physically, the primary events are still the same as you have with the regular touch. Note that even the mouse button down event can be \"real\" (touchpad has physical buttons, usually) or emulated, through the quick touch and them move. I don't really know where this simulation happens, in some piece of firmware or the driver, but I would rather guess it happens in the driver, that's it, at the expense of the computer's CPU. Some elements of \"IA\" are involved: recognition of the touch.\r\n\r\nAnd we all know that the recognition can give you false positives and false negatives. And if the quality of the combination of the hardware (including firmware) and the driver is questionable, or some part of it is out of tune, the recognition results can be inadequate. Unfortunately, I failed to explain different results for different software; but it could be timing, the level of CPU load at the moment, anything which tends to confuse low-quality firmware or software\u2026 :-) I don't really know consistent experimental results to tell anything more certainly.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov27-May-15 17:09pm27-May-15 18:06pm"]},
{"question": "Best aproach for reacting on other software", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Personally I would create a centralised WCF service that monitors the phone system. Your service should then turn the captured commands into events that could be pushed (published) to subscribing applications. This would be a fairly large task upfront however this would make an \"Ideal\" approach.\r\n\r\nMost phone systems have an API that can be hooked into. If your PBX has this I would \"Improve Question\" and include the make of the phone system. \r\n\r\nPersonally I don't rate COM but I could be very wrong.\r\ndb7uk"]},
{"question": "Best aproach for reacting on other software", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Personally I would create a centralised WCF service that monitors the phone system. Your service should then turn the captured commands into events that could be pushed (published) to subscribing applications. This would be a fairly large task upfront however this would make an \"Ideal\" approach.\r\n\r\nMost phone systems have an API that can be hooked into. If your PBX has this I would \"Improve Question\" and include the make of the phone system. \r\n\r\nPersonally I don't rate COM but I could be very wrong.\r\ndb7uk"]},
{"question": "Install React Native on really old PC", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    To be honest with you, I wouldn't even try: VS 2008 on it's own has a minimum requirements\r\nof: \r\n1.6 GHz or faster processor\r\n384 MB of RAM or more\r\n2.2 GB of available hard-disk space\r\n\r\nBut I wouldn't even think of running XP in less than 1GB, and preferably 2GB. And that 20GB HDD is going to be pretty tight as well...\r\n\r\nFind the money and fix your broken one: it's going to save you a fortune in time!\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Well, this is a tough case\u2026\r\n\r\nEven old not-so-good Windows XP along makes little to no sense of such configuration. I think Linux would be much better choice, and even not just Linux, but better some really lightweight distro. Most likely, you would want it with desktop environment and something Windows-like, then Lubuntu (Ubuntu based on lightweight LXDE desktop) would be one of the best choices.\r\n\r\nI have no idea why would you need Visual Studio; you know better. If you need to do JavaScript development with ReactJS, which is nothing but a JavaScript library, then, strictly speaking, you only need a Web browser and some text editor. On your configuration, even a big IDE on Linux could be slow, but it's hard to say, you just can try.\r\n\r\nThe problem of answering you is that I don't know what you really need and what not.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi, thanks for the responses. Perhaps my tag \"ReactJs\" is misleading, Iused it because there is no \"React Native\" tag defined.\r\n\r\nReact Native is normally installed with npm, which during installing uses node-gyp, which on Win has Visual C++ compiler as dependancy. React Native seems to do a lot, like create project file structure, provide js libraries and native libraries for the native part of hybrid app, creates a build file for building the app ect. I as a newbie am probably best off using their recommended route.\r\nMember 12187094", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi again, istalled Lubuntu as recommended and works fine on the old pc. Built the React-Native and dependencies libs (on linux you can use gcc for node-gyp)and managed to build release APK for Android, just in case anybody is interested regarding really old PC\r\nConcerning WinXP SP3 on the PC, Ive been using the PC with that OS in the basement for years and in my opinion worked OK\r\nMember 12187094"]},
{"question": "Install React Native on really old PC", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    To be honest with you, I wouldn't even try: VS 2008 on it's own has a minimum requirements\r\nof: \r\n1.6 GHz or faster processor\r\n384 MB of RAM or more\r\n2.2 GB of available hard-disk space\r\n\r\nBut I wouldn't even think of running XP in less than 1GB, and preferably 2GB. And that 20GB HDD is going to be pretty tight as well...\r\n\r\nFind the money and fix your broken one: it's going to save you a fortune in time!\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Well, this is a tough case\u2026\r\n\r\nEven old not-so-good Windows XP along makes little to no sense of such configuration. I think Linux would be much better choice, and even not just Linux, but better some really lightweight distro. Most likely, you would want it with desktop environment and something Windows-like, then Lubuntu (Ubuntu based on lightweight LXDE desktop) would be one of the best choices.\r\n\r\nI have no idea why would you need Visual Studio; you know better. If you need to do JavaScript development with ReactJS, which is nothing but a JavaScript library, then, strictly speaking, you only need a Web browser and some text editor. On your configuration, even a big IDE on Linux could be slow, but it's hard to say, you just can try.\r\n\r\nThe problem of answering you is that I don't know what you really need and what not.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi, thanks for the responses. Perhaps my tag \"ReactJs\" is misleading, Iused it because there is no \"React Native\" tag defined.\r\n\r\nReact Native is normally installed with npm, which during installing uses node-gyp, which on Win has Visual C++ compiler as dependancy. React Native seems to do a lot, like create project file structure, provide js libraries and native libraries for the native part of hybrid app, creates a build file for building the app ect. I as a newbie am probably best off using their recommended route.\r\nMember 12187094", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi again, istalled Lubuntu as recommended and works fine on the old pc. Built the React-Native and dependencies libs (on linux you can use gcc for node-gyp)and managed to build release APK for Android, just in case anybody is interested regarding really old PC\r\nConcerning WinXP SP3 on the PC, Ive been using the PC with that OS in the basement for years and in my opinion worked OK\r\nMember 12187094"]},
{"question": "Can you we use react, js with ASP.NET core for product development", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    React.js is surely a popular choice, see overview and pros and cons here: [] \r\nAs it is written and tested by FaceBook, you would expect it to function well with a big application.\r\nRickZeeland"]},
{"question": "Form builder application with wizard multiple steps in react js", "answers": []},
{"question": "What is the difference between bootstrap and other js framwork like react?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Read the Pros and Cons here: []\r\nAlso see: []\r\nRickZeeland"]},
{"question": "Make a GridSplitter react to the visibility of the grid content", "answers": []},
{"question": "What should I learn before start angular js and react js?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    \r\nSince you didn't tell what you already know, a good tutorial site about what you need to master to build web apps.\r\n[]\r\nPatrice T31-May-17 3:10am"]},
{"question": "What should I learn before start angular js and react js?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    \r\nSince you didn't tell what you already know, a good tutorial site about what you need to master to build web apps.\r\n[]\r\nPatrice T31-May-17 3:10am"]},
{"question": "How to fetch image using api react native", "answers": []},
{"question": "dropdown menu selection?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    How about a []?\r\n\r\nThat one reacts to the Menu Event and gets the MenuItem, the Event was fired on. Should be simple to react on that.\r\nTorstenH.", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    i need the dropmenu to have different names of games, like when you open the dropmenu it says game1 and further down game 2, and so on. When you fx select game 2, then it open a new window with game2.\r\nDo i then need to create a new .java file, with game2?\r\nvegapede30-Jun-11 11:06am"]},
{"question": "File upload not working in httpcontext", "answers": []},
{"question": "Check-Box react as Radio  Button using C#", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Make a List of Checkboxes and use the same event handler for all of them.\r\nWhenever one is selected store it's index in temp variable, make all checkboxes 'unchecked', then check the one you stored.\r\nBacchusBeale17-Mar-15 0:14am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    First of all, if you know this is not a good solution, you should not do it. The person who gave you this \"requirement\" could be not competent enough, so you need to convince him/her. This is one of your responsibilities, one of the pretty difficult ones. This is like preventing crime.\r\n\r\nIt it was a good thing to do, looking for a solution would be a bad idea. Such things should be done from first principles, using original documentation. No wonder you could not find anything \u2014 this is way too trivial to write and article on this, or just an answer. \r\n\r\nBesides, you did not even indicate what is CheckBox. Which one? Do you think there is only one type with this name? No. This name is ambiguous, so you really need to give us full type name. In all cases, you simply handle the event invoked when a checked state is changed, and change properties in the handler.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov17-Mar-15 0:25am17-Mar-15 0:44am17-Mar-15 0:48am17-Mar-15 6:37am17-Mar-15 1:20am"]},
{"question": "C# WPF best way to run method/or check in background to check if condition hits", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Have you considered setting up the property to fire a custom event when its value changes, and then have an event handler in the form that reacts to the event? No threads needed.\r\n#realJSOP4-Jun-20 9:39am4-Jun-20 12:05pm4-Jun-20 13:03pm5-Jun-20 14:07pm"]},
{"question": "What is the error in my code?", "answers": []},
{"question": "How do I implement recaptcha using reactjs with a PHP backend", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Have a look here: []\r\nOriginalGriff"]},
{"question": "App:installdebug exception in lenovo A7000 plus mobile using react native", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Sometimes you'll need a specific USB driver for the type of phone. First place I would go is the phone manufacturer support area looking for USB drivers. If they have one marked for debug that would be a plus.\r\nAlso, you might have to turn on the debugging ability. In the Samsung and the Google Pixel phones that I use I had to go to the settings, then system, then 'about phone'. Scroll to the bottom and tap the 'build number' 7 times. Close and reopen settings (might not be necessary) and you should see a 'developer options' settings item where you can enable various debugging options.\r\n\r\nHTH, Mike\r\nMike V Baker"]},
{"question": "How to play/pause video on scrolling a list of videos in reactjs", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    []\r\nMember 14939628"]},
{"question": "React native iOS build clang: error: linker command failed with exit code 1 (use -v to see invocation)", "answers": []},
{"question": "App:installdebug exception in lenovo A7000 plus mobile using react native", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Sometimes you'll need a specific USB driver for the type of phone. First place I would go is the phone manufacturer support area looking for USB drivers. If they have one marked for debug that would be a plus.\r\nAlso, you might have to turn on the debugging ability. In the Samsung and the Google Pixel phones that I use I had to go to the settings, then system, then 'about phone'. Scroll to the bottom and tap the 'build number' 7 times. Close and reopen settings (might not be necessary) and you should see a 'developer options' settings item where you can enable various debugging options.\r\n\r\nHTH, Mike\r\nMike V Baker"]},
{"question": null, "answers": []},
{"question": "Cant able to implement social login in react native", "answers": []},
{"question": "Show bootstrap modal with custom title using react JS", "answers": []},
{"question": "my program has stopped to react with WMI Events", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Add a handler for the Stopped event, and see if you receive it when the watcher is stopped. If you do, the event mechanism is working fine. The disposed event handler is also different from either EventsArrived and Stopped, so if you were expecting to see an EventArrived event from either stopping or disposing your watcher, you won't see those events unless you have handlers for them.\r\n#realJSOP28-Oct-10 23:58pm"]},
{"question": "How do I preload images using react VR?", "answers": []},
{"question": "my program has stopped to react with WMI Events", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Add a handler for the Stopped event, and see if you receive it when the watcher is stopped. If you do, the event mechanism is working fine. The disposed event handler is also different from either EventsArrived and Stopped, so if you were expecting to see an EventArrived event from either stopping or disposing your watcher, you won't see those events unless you have handlers for them.\r\n#realJSOP28-Oct-10 23:58pm"]},
{"question": "What is the difference between bootstrap and other js framwork like react?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Read the Pros and Cons here: []\r\nAlso see: []\r\nRickZeeland"]},
{"question": "Install React Native on really old PC", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    To be honest with you, I wouldn't even try: VS 2008 on it's own has a minimum requirements\r\nof: \r\n1.6 GHz or faster processor\r\n384 MB of RAM or more\r\n2.2 GB of available hard-disk space\r\n\r\nBut I wouldn't even think of running XP in less than 1GB, and preferably 2GB. And that 20GB HDD is going to be pretty tight as well...\r\n\r\nFind the money and fix your broken one: it's going to save you a fortune in time!\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Well, this is a tough case\u2026\r\n\r\nEven old not-so-good Windows XP along makes little to no sense of such configuration. I think Linux would be much better choice, and even not just Linux, but better some really lightweight distro. Most likely, you would want it with desktop environment and something Windows-like, then Lubuntu (Ubuntu based on lightweight LXDE desktop) would be one of the best choices.\r\n\r\nI have no idea why would you need Visual Studio; you know better. If you need to do JavaScript development with ReactJS, which is nothing but a JavaScript library, then, strictly speaking, you only need a Web browser and some text editor. On your configuration, even a big IDE on Linux could be slow, but it's hard to say, you just can try.\r\n\r\nThe problem of answering you is that I don't know what you really need and what not.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi, thanks for the responses. Perhaps my tag \"ReactJs\" is misleading, Iused it because there is no \"React Native\" tag defined.\r\n\r\nReact Native is normally installed with npm, which during installing uses node-gyp, which on Win has Visual C++ compiler as dependancy. React Native seems to do a lot, like create project file structure, provide js libraries and native libraries for the native part of hybrid app, creates a build file for building the app ect. I as a newbie am probably best off using their recommended route.\r\nMember 12187094", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi again, istalled Lubuntu as recommended and works fine on the old pc. Built the React-Native and dependencies libs (on linux you can use gcc for node-gyp)and managed to build release APK for Android, just in case anybody is interested regarding really old PC\r\nConcerning WinXP SP3 on the PC, Ive been using the PC with that OS in the basement for years and in my opinion worked OK\r\nMember 12187094"]},
{"question": "Serving react web page from a flask web server", "answers": []},
{"question": "Install React Native on really old PC", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    To be honest with you, I wouldn't even try: VS 2008 on it's own has a minimum requirements\r\nof: \r\n1.6 GHz or faster processor\r\n384 MB of RAM or more\r\n2.2 GB of available hard-disk space\r\n\r\nBut I wouldn't even think of running XP in less than 1GB, and preferably 2GB. And that 20GB HDD is going to be pretty tight as well...\r\n\r\nFind the money and fix your broken one: it's going to save you a fortune in time!\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Well, this is a tough case\u2026\r\n\r\nEven old not-so-good Windows XP along makes little to no sense of such configuration. I think Linux would be much better choice, and even not just Linux, but better some really lightweight distro. Most likely, you would want it with desktop environment and something Windows-like, then Lubuntu (Ubuntu based on lightweight LXDE desktop) would be one of the best choices.\r\n\r\nI have no idea why would you need Visual Studio; you know better. If you need to do JavaScript development with ReactJS, which is nothing but a JavaScript library, then, strictly speaking, you only need a Web browser and some text editor. On your configuration, even a big IDE on Linux could be slow, but it's hard to say, you just can try.\r\n\r\nThe problem of answering you is that I don't know what you really need and what not.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi, thanks for the responses. Perhaps my tag \"ReactJs\" is misleading, Iused it because there is no \"React Native\" tag defined.\r\n\r\nReact Native is normally installed with npm, which during installing uses node-gyp, which on Win has Visual C++ compiler as dependancy. React Native seems to do a lot, like create project file structure, provide js libraries and native libraries for the native part of hybrid app, creates a build file for building the app ect. I as a newbie am probably best off using their recommended route.\r\nMember 12187094", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi again, istalled Lubuntu as recommended and works fine on the old pc. Built the React-Native and dependencies libs (on linux you can use gcc for node-gyp)and managed to build release APK for Android, just in case anybody is interested regarding really old PC\r\nConcerning WinXP SP3 on the PC, Ive been using the PC with that OS in the basement for years and in my opinion worked OK\r\nMember 12187094"]},
{"question": "Install React Native on really old PC", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    To be honest with you, I wouldn't even try: VS 2008 on it's own has a minimum requirements\r\nof: \r\n1.6 GHz or faster processor\r\n384 MB of RAM or more\r\n2.2 GB of available hard-disk space\r\n\r\nBut I wouldn't even think of running XP in less than 1GB, and preferably 2GB. And that 20GB HDD is going to be pretty tight as well...\r\n\r\nFind the money and fix your broken one: it's going to save you a fortune in time!\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Well, this is a tough case\u2026\r\n\r\nEven old not-so-good Windows XP along makes little to no sense of such configuration. I think Linux would be much better choice, and even not just Linux, but better some really lightweight distro. Most likely, you would want it with desktop environment and something Windows-like, then Lubuntu (Ubuntu based on lightweight LXDE desktop) would be one of the best choices.\r\n\r\nI have no idea why would you need Visual Studio; you know better. If you need to do JavaScript development with ReactJS, which is nothing but a JavaScript library, then, strictly speaking, you only need a Web browser and some text editor. On your configuration, even a big IDE on Linux could be slow, but it's hard to say, you just can try.\r\n\r\nThe problem of answering you is that I don't know what you really need and what not.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi, thanks for the responses. Perhaps my tag \"ReactJs\" is misleading, Iused it because there is no \"React Native\" tag defined.\r\n\r\nReact Native is normally installed with npm, which during installing uses node-gyp, which on Win has Visual C++ compiler as dependancy. React Native seems to do a lot, like create project file structure, provide js libraries and native libraries for the native part of hybrid app, creates a build file for building the app ect. I as a newbie am probably best off using their recommended route.\r\nMember 12187094", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi again, istalled Lubuntu as recommended and works fine on the old pc. Built the React-Native and dependencies libs (on linux you can use gcc for node-gyp)and managed to build release APK for Android, just in case anybody is interested regarding really old PC\r\nConcerning WinXP SP3 on the PC, Ive been using the PC with that OS in the basement for years and in my opinion worked OK\r\nMember 12187094"]},
{"question": "Check-Box react as Radio  Button using C#", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Make a List of Checkboxes and use the same event handler for all of them.\r\nWhenever one is selected store it's index in temp variable, make all checkboxes 'unchecked', then check the one you stored.\r\nBacchusBeale17-Mar-15 0:14am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    First of all, if you know this is not a good solution, you should not do it. The person who gave you this \"requirement\" could be not competent enough, so you need to convince him/her. This is one of your responsibilities, one of the pretty difficult ones. This is like preventing crime.\r\n\r\nIt it was a good thing to do, looking for a solution would be a bad idea. Such things should be done from first principles, using original documentation. No wonder you could not find anything \u2014 this is way too trivial to write and article on this, or just an answer. \r\n\r\nBesides, you did not even indicate what is CheckBox. Which one? Do you think there is only one type with this name? No. This name is ambiguous, so you really need to give us full type name. In all cases, you simply handle the event invoked when a checked state is changed, and change properties in the handler.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov17-Mar-15 0:25am17-Mar-15 0:44am17-Mar-15 0:48am17-Mar-15 6:37am17-Mar-15 1:20am"]},
{"question": "Problem in setting up the react native environment", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    react-native init ProjectName --version 0.55.4\r\n\r\nThis worked for me!\r\nJanardhanam Julapalli"]},
{"question": "Storing the web api urls for a react or reactredux application", "answers": []},
{"question": "Problem with checkbox onchange on react JS doesn't work properly", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to integrate react js in visual studio", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to read the current URL in the react application", "answers": []},
{"question": "Problem in setting up the react native environment", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    react-native init ProjectName --version 0.55.4\r\n\r\nThis worked for me!\r\nJanardhanam Julapalli"]},
{"question": "Can you we use react, js with ASP.NET core for product development", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    React.js is surely a popular choice, see overview and pros and cons here: [] \r\nAs it is written and tested by FaceBook, you would expect it to function well with a big application.\r\nRickZeeland"]},
{"question": "Twitter code reacting tweets", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to react to touchpad scrolling in WPF?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Basically, my advice is in the discussion in comments to the question.\r\n\r\nYou are welcome.\r\n\r\nLet me put some speculations here. I hope we are about to close this issue, because further steps can be out of our reach.\r\n\r\nAccording to your description, your code does nothing by handling the mouse wheel event (next time, better show where you add the event handler to the invocation tree of some event instance, that is, corresponding += operator, because the method name customTileController_MouseWheel, strictly speaking, does not tell anything about it; also, never use such auto-generated names, they violate good Microsoft naming conventions, for some apparent reasons). It cannot be wrong.\r\n\r\nFirst of all, all input events available in .NET are of different levels. Some are primary and are generated by the hardware and are pushed to the system through the hardware interrupts one some IRQ line and handled by the hardware driver, and some are secondary. For example, hardware events produce KeyDown and KeyUp events (also indirectly), but not KeyPress event, which is secondary to the first two; it comes into play after a long chain taking into account input language, to produce a character which does not exist on lower level.\r\n\r\nThis is not what happens to physical mouse wheel. When you roll it, hardware generates the event of the same level as, say, mouse move, even though in mouse move of an optical mouse, optical image recognition takes place. Anyway, , these are the events of the same level. The roll of the mouse cannot be misinterpreted as mouse move.\r\n\r\nWhat happens in the touchpad \"scroll\" area? Nothing like that. Instead, some code is  to emulate the same effect as the \"real mouse\" does. Physically, the primary events are still the same as you have with the regular touch. Note that even the mouse button down event can be \"real\" (touchpad has physical buttons, usually) or emulated, through the quick touch and them move. I don't really know where this simulation happens, in some piece of firmware or the driver, but I would rather guess it happens in the driver, that's it, at the expense of the computer's CPU. Some elements of \"IA\" are involved: recognition of the touch.\r\n\r\nAnd we all know that the recognition can give you false positives and false negatives. And if the quality of the combination of the hardware (including firmware) and the driver is questionable, or some part of it is out of tune, the recognition results can be inadequate. Unfortunately, I failed to explain different results for different software; but it could be timing, the level of CPU load at the moment, anything which tends to confuse low-quality firmware or software\u2026 :-) I don't really know consistent experimental results to tell anything more certainly.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov27-May-15 17:09pm27-May-15 18:06pm"]},
{"question": "React call a component with onclick", "answers": []},
{"question": "React to jframe close action in an actionlistener", "answers": []},
{"question": "Variable type reacting to sound?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    See [] and  [].\r\nRichard MacCutchan"]},
{"question": "Booking.com map widget doesn't load when using history.push() with react", "answers": []},
{"question": "Proper way on how to install and add an audio file in react native?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Sorry, but this site does not provide code to order. And the expression  tells us nothing that would lead us to suggested solutions.\r\nRichard MacCutchan", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It would not work on its own. You have to configure the project to run properly, and also make sure that you are using the valid file types. This package react-audio-player uses the native <audio /> tag to provide the service, and this HTML5 element is known to have some limitations for the file types that it can run ().\r\n\r\nCheck more on the package here at NPM: [] \r\n[]\r\nAfzaal Ahmad Zeeshan"]},
{"question": "This.setstate not working in react js", "answers": []},
{"question": "Proper way on how to install and add an audio file in react native?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Sorry, but this site does not provide code to order. And the expression  tells us nothing that would lead us to suggested solutions.\r\nRichard MacCutchan", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It would not work on its own. You have to configure the project to run properly, and also make sure that you are using the valid file types. This package react-audio-player uses the native <audio /> tag to provide the service, and this HTML5 element is known to have some limitations for the file types that it can run ().\r\n\r\nCheck more on the package here at NPM: [] \r\n[]\r\nAfzaal Ahmad Zeeshan"]},
{"question": "Check-Box react as Radio  Button using C#", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Make a List of Checkboxes and use the same event handler for all of them.\r\nWhenever one is selected store it's index in temp variable, make all checkboxes 'unchecked', then check the one you stored.\r\nBacchusBeale17-Mar-15 0:14am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    First of all, if you know this is not a good solution, you should not do it. The person who gave you this \"requirement\" could be not competent enough, so you need to convince him/her. This is one of your responsibilities, one of the pretty difficult ones. This is like preventing crime.\r\n\r\nIt it was a good thing to do, looking for a solution would be a bad idea. Such things should be done from first principles, using original documentation. No wonder you could not find anything \u2014 this is way too trivial to write and article on this, or just an answer. \r\n\r\nBesides, you did not even indicate what is CheckBox. Which one? Do you think there is only one type with this name? No. This name is ambiguous, so you really need to give us full type name. In all cases, you simply handle the event invoked when a checked state is changed, and change properties in the handler.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov17-Mar-15 0:25am17-Mar-15 0:44am17-Mar-15 0:48am17-Mar-15 6:37am17-Mar-15 1:20am"]},
{"question": "How do I fix support for the experimental syntax 'decorators-legacy' isn't currently enabled error in react native expo", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    []\r\nRichard MacCutchan29-Oct-20 14:05pm29-Oct-20 14:16pm29-Oct-20 14:33pm"]},
{"question": "How to submit input to node js service from react JS UI", "answers": []},
{"question": "Code not reacting to inputs", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    This is my full code\r\n\r\n<pre>package com.company;\r\nimport java.util.Scanner;\r\n\r\npublic class Main {\r\n    //prints string to console\r\n    private static void print(String s) {\r\n        System.out.println(s);\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    //all the constants for given R values returns the correct R value\r\n    private static double rValues(String pressure){\r\n        double R = 0;\r\n        if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"atm\")){\r\n            R = 0.082057338;\r\n        }else if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"tor\")){\r\n            R = 62.363577;\r\n        }else if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"mmHg\")){\r\n            R = 62.36367;\r\n        }\r\n        return R;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    //all of the equations solved for unknown variable\r\n    private static double solve_P(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature ){\r\n        double exitP;\r\n        exitP = (variables[2]*temperature*constant)/variables[1];\r\n        return exitP;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_V(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature){\r\n        double exitV;\r\n        exitV =(variables[2]*temperature*constant)/variables[0];\r\n        return exitV;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_n(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature){\r\n        double exitN;\r\n        exitN = (variables[0]*variables[1])/(constant*temperature);\r\n        return exitN;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_T(double[] variables, double constant){\r\n        double exitT;\r\n        exitT = (variables[0]*variables[1])/(constant*variables[2]);\r\n        return exitT;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n    public static void main(String[] args) {\r\n\r\n        //play again loop\r\n        boolean isRunning = true;\r\n        String playAgain;\r\n        while (isRunning) {\r\n\r\n            Scanner keyboard = new Scanner(System.in);//creates scanner\r\n\r\n            //introduction\r\n            print(\"This is an ideal gas law solver\");\r\n            print(\"PV=nRT\");\r\n\r\n            //what R value to use\r\n            print(\"what is the pressure measured in?\");\r\n            print(\"atm, tor, or mmmHg\");\r\n            print(\">\");\r\n            String whatPressure;\r\n            whatPressure = keyboard.next();\r\n            double rConstant;\r\n            rConstant = rValues(whatPressure);\r\n\r\n            //stored questions\r\n            String[] userQuestions = {\"what is the pressure P\",\r\n                    \"what is the volume V\",\r\n                    \"what is the number of moles n\"};\r\n\r\n            //stores answers in userAnswers\r\n            double[] userAnswers = new double[3];\r\n\r\n            print(\"what variable would you like to solve for?\");\r\n            String unknownVariable;\r\n            unknownVariable = keyboard.next();\r\n            System.out.println(\"solving for \" + unknownVariable);\r\n\r\n            //converts between celsius and kelvin\r\n            double temperature = 0;\r\n            if (unknownVariable.compareToIgnoreCase(\"T\") == 0) {\r\n                print(\"what is the temperature in?\");\r\n                print(\"kelvin (K) or celsius (c) \");\r\n                String whatTemperatureUnit;\r\n                whatTemperatureUnit = keyboard.next();\r\n                print(\"what is the temperature?\");\r\n                temperature = keyboard.nextDouble();\r\n                if (whatTemperatureUnit\r\nMember 1377085311-Apr-18 4:32am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It is not by mistake: your code is  to do that.\r\nCPallini"]},
{"question": "How do I fix support for the experimental syntax 'decorators-legacy' isn't currently enabled error in react native expo", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    []\r\nRichard MacCutchan29-Oct-20 14:05pm29-Oct-20 14:16pm29-Oct-20 14:33pm"]},
{"question": "Code not reacting to inputs", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    This is my full code\r\n\r\n<pre>package com.company;\r\nimport java.util.Scanner;\r\n\r\npublic class Main {\r\n    //prints string to console\r\n    private static void print(String s) {\r\n        System.out.println(s);\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    //all the constants for given R values returns the correct R value\r\n    private static double rValues(String pressure){\r\n        double R = 0;\r\n        if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"atm\")){\r\n            R = 0.082057338;\r\n        }else if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"tor\")){\r\n            R = 62.363577;\r\n        }else if(pressure.equalsIgnoreCase(\"mmHg\")){\r\n            R = 62.36367;\r\n        }\r\n        return R;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    //all of the equations solved for unknown variable\r\n    private static double solve_P(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature ){\r\n        double exitP;\r\n        exitP = (variables[2]*temperature*constant)/variables[1];\r\n        return exitP;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_V(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature){\r\n        double exitV;\r\n        exitV =(variables[2]*temperature*constant)/variables[0];\r\n        return exitV;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_n(double[] variables, double constant, double temperature){\r\n        double exitN;\r\n        exitN = (variables[0]*variables[1])/(constant*temperature);\r\n        return exitN;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    private static double solve_T(double[] variables, double constant){\r\n        double exitT;\r\n        exitT = (variables[0]*variables[1])/(constant*variables[2]);\r\n        return exitT;\r\n    }\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n    public static void main(String[] args) {\r\n\r\n        //play again loop\r\n        boolean isRunning = true;\r\n        String playAgain;\r\n        while (isRunning) {\r\n\r\n            Scanner keyboard = new Scanner(System.in);//creates scanner\r\n\r\n            //introduction\r\n            print(\"This is an ideal gas law solver\");\r\n            print(\"PV=nRT\");\r\n\r\n            //what R value to use\r\n            print(\"what is the pressure measured in?\");\r\n            print(\"atm, tor, or mmmHg\");\r\n            print(\">\");\r\n            String whatPressure;\r\n            whatPressure = keyboard.next();\r\n            double rConstant;\r\n            rConstant = rValues(whatPressure);\r\n\r\n            //stored questions\r\n            String[] userQuestions = {\"what is the pressure P\",\r\n                    \"what is the volume V\",\r\n                    \"what is the number of moles n\"};\r\n\r\n            //stores answers in userAnswers\r\n            double[] userAnswers = new double[3];\r\n\r\n            print(\"what variable would you like to solve for?\");\r\n            String unknownVariable;\r\n            unknownVariable = keyboard.next();\r\n            System.out.println(\"solving for \" + unknownVariable);\r\n\r\n            //converts between celsius and kelvin\r\n            double temperature = 0;\r\n            if (unknownVariable.compareToIgnoreCase(\"T\") == 0) {\r\n                print(\"what is the temperature in?\");\r\n                print(\"kelvin (K) or celsius (c) \");\r\n                String whatTemperatureUnit;\r\n                whatTemperatureUnit = keyboard.next();\r\n                print(\"what is the temperature?\");\r\n                temperature = keyboard.nextDouble();\r\n                if (whatTemperatureUnit\r\nMember 1377085311-Apr-18 4:32am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It is not by mistake: your code is  to do that.\r\nCPallini"]},
{"question": "How do I update input field value dynamically- react", "answers": []},
{"question": "How do I solve react cannot perform state update on my page?", "answers": []},
{"question": "How do I get a toast notification when a item is added to cart in react JS", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    This may help: []\r\nRichard MacCutchan8-Nov-20 0:53amtoast.configure()"]},
{"question": "React native: there is way to view the list of the \u201czone_name\u201d into flatlist from sqlite table?", "answers": []},
{"question": "How do I implement a local storage functionality in my shopping cart? - React JS", "answers": []},
{"question": "Type error: cannot read property 'map' of null - react JS", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    How have you defined products is still not clear. I can just guess that its initialized as null in your component and that is causing an error. \r\n\r\nmap works only on arrays. So, check products is defined array before doing map on it.\r\nTry this and see:\r\nif(products)\r\n{\r\n  products.map((product, index) => (\r\n    <li key={index}>\r\n      <h2>{product.name}</h2>\r\n      <div className=\"space3\"></div>\r\n      <img src={product.image} alt={product.name} />\r\n      <div className=\"space\"></div>\r\n      <div className=\"buy-product\">\r\n        <button onClick={() => (window.location.href = product.link)}>\r\n          Buy\r\n        </button>\r\n      </div>\r\n      <h4>${product.cost}</h4>\r\n      <div className=\"cart-container\">\r\n        <div className=\"space2\"></div>\r\n        <div className=\"product-icon\">\r\n          <a className=\"cart\" onClick={() => addToCart(product)}>\r\n            <FaCartPlus />\r\n          </a>\r\n        </div>\r\n      </div>\r\n    </li>\r\n  ))}\r\n}\r\nIf that doesn't solve, look at the other possible reasons here and troubleshoot: []\r\n12-Nov-20 2:44am\r\n<ul className=\"flex cards\">\r\n          {if (products) {\r\n            products.map((product, index) => (\r\n            <li key={index}>\r\n              <h2>{product.name}</h2>\r\n              <div className=\"space3\"></div>\r\n              <img src={product.image} alt={product.name} />\r\n              <div className=\"space\"></div>\r\n              <div className=\"buy-product\">\r\n                <button onClick={() => (window.location.href = product.link)}>\r\n                  Buy\r\n                </button>\r\n              </div>\r\n              <h4>${product.cost}</h4>\r\n              <div className=\"cart-container\">\r\n                <div className=\"space2\"></div>\r\n                <div className=\"product-icon\">\r\n                  <a className=\"cart\" onClick={() => addToCart(product)}>\r\n                    <FaCartPlus />\r\n                  </a>\r\n                </div>\r\n              </div>\r\n            </li>\r\n          ))\r\n          }}\r\n        </ul>\r\n12-Nov-20 2:51am12-Nov-20 2:55am12-Nov-20 4:30am12-Nov-20 21:35pmHideExpandCopy Codeif (item) {    return (      <div className=\"products\">        <h1 className=\"big-text\">Games</h1>        {/* Cards */}        <div className=\"products\">          <ul className=\"flex cards\">            {products.map((product, index) => (              <li key={index}>                <h2>{product.name}</h2>                <div className=\"space3\"></div>                <img src={product.image} alt={product.name} />                <div className=\"space\"></div>                <div className=\"buy-product\">                  <button onClick={() => (window.location.href = product.link)}>                    Buy                  </button>                </div>                <h4>${product.cost}</h4>                <div className=\"cart-container\">                  <div className=\"space2\"></div>                  <div className=\"product-icon\">                    <a className=\"cart\" onClick={() => addToCart(product)}>                      <FaCartPlus />                    </a>                  </div>                </div>              </li>            ))}          </ul>        </div>      </div>    );  }12-Nov-20 3:59am"]},
{"question": "Meteor / react: create mongodb entries by form inputs and \u201cclicking\u201d inputs", "answers": []},
{"question": "How can I develop ecommerce site by prestashop platform with nodejs and react?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    The fairly obvious answer is that you study each of these subjects in depth and learn how to get them to work together to do what you want. There is no shortcut to becoming an experienced developer, only practice, practice, practice.\r\nRichard MacCutchan9-Aug-20 5:54am9-Aug-20 7:15am9-Aug-20 15:14pm"]},
{"question": "How can I develop ecommerce site by prestashop platform with nodejs and react?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    The fairly obvious answer is that you study each of these subjects in depth and learn how to get them to work together to do what you want. There is no shortcut to becoming an experienced developer, only practice, practice, practice.\r\nRichard MacCutchan9-Aug-20 5:54am9-Aug-20 7:15am9-Aug-20 15:14pm"]},
{"question": "React - how to make common component to use on all pages", "answers": []},
{"question": "Which react/JS project should I build for my 1st job portfolio?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It is impossible to answer such a question, without knowing more about you, and more about the jobs that are available. And this site is not the place to find the answers; this is for programming questions. All I would say is, look at other websites and try to see what things are good and what bad, and create a design from what you see and learn.\r\nRichard MacCutchan24-Sep-20 17:16pm24-Sep-20 17:21pm"]},
{"question": "How do I get a toast notification when a item is added to cart in react JS", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    This may help: []\r\nRichard MacCutchan8-Nov-20 0:53amtoast.configure()"]},
{"question": null, "answers": []}
]